Are you ready to light up the night, Chicago?
I, I, I was walking in the shadows I was living in
the gray Waiting for a signal To help me find my
way
I can feel a new connection Like a spark inside
the dark You're my one true direction You're the
fire, you're the spark We're gonna light up the
night Chasing the stars till the morning light
We're gonna make it alright Turning our color on
Shining so bright
We're gonna light up the night
The city sleeps, but we're awake A promise that
will never break The future's ours, I see the
sign Just put your hand in mine I can feel a new
connection Like a spark inside the dark You're
my one true direction You're the fire You're the
spark. We're gonna light up the night. Oh, oh,
oh. Chasing the stars till the morning light.
We're gonna make it all right. Oh, oh, oh.
Turning our color on. Shining so bright. We're
gonna light up the night.
Hey!
Woo!
Let's light it up. We're gonna light up the
night. Oh, oh, oh. Chasing the stars till the
morning light. We're gonna make it all right.
Oh, oh, oh. Turning our color on. Shining so
bright.
We're gonna light up the night.
We love
you!